# **ALBI**

## **DOUGLAS-WALLER**

Game Developer

34 Mill Hill Wombwell, Barnsley \$738\$J 07542991614 https://albi-back.github.io/portfolio/ Albiwall1@gmail.com

### **Education**

7 GCSEs 4-6 (2014-2019) at Netherwood Academy

Level 3 diploma in Game design at Barnsley College

Level 5 in Computer Science for games at Sheffield Hallam University

## **Experience**

Experience Warehouse operative at Cranswick Barnsley under the Best Connection Group (2021)

Various volunteer work at comic conventions (2022-present)

Student casual worker(mentor) (Sept 2024-present)

## **Professional skills**

Proficient in multiple programming languages, including C# and C++, with a strong adaptability to any derivative language within the C language family.

Extensive knowledge of the Unity game engine, coupled with a solid understanding of DirectX, enabling me to create complex and immersive scenes in both platforms.

## **Technical Knowledge**

Unity C++ C# Python DirectX 11 HTML Java

References available upon request.



## **Competencies**

Character programming | Enemy A.I. programming

### **Profile**

Enthusiastic and dedicated individual with a strong background in leadership and mentoring. As a former Boy Scout, I developed essential skills in teamwork, resilience, and community service, while honing my leadership abilities. My experience as a prefect in high school and a course representative in sixth form has equipped me with excellent communication and organizational skills, allowing me to effectively represent and support my peers. Currently, as a student mentor at university, I enjoy guiding and motivating others to achieve their academic goals. Additionally, I am a passionate guitarist, which has enhanced my creativity and discipline. I am committed to fostering a positive and collaborative environment in all my endeavours.

#### **Personal Skills**

Innovative, confident, and positive. I am a good communicator and have a can-do attitude and can find the positive of any situation and I am good at both teamwork and independent tasks.

#### **Hobbies**

Guitar, Bass Ukulele, Reading, Rock Climbing, Cinema, Gaming.